[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":31624,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":58204,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":7546,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":65751,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"15","response_history":["15"],"rt":19586,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":85339,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1331,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":86671,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"12","response_history":["12"],"rt":6107,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":92780,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":14918,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":107699,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 o r bigger , you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":12219,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":119919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":8690,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":128611,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"8","response_history":["8"],"rt":10096,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":138707,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1119,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":139827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":4088,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":143917,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":5370,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":149287,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"Wha t is 4 + <sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"8","response_history":["8"],"rt":18971,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":168258,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":5463,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":173722,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"f ree","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"10","response_history":["10+","10"],"rt":6622,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":180345,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1840,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":182186,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":6370,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":188557,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<s ub>6</su b> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1388,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":189946,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":9062,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":199009,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":829,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":199839,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start w ith the  first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3421,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":203261,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1212,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":204474,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"12","response_history":["6","12"],"rt":6152,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":210629,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0 because 3 + 3 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1244,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":211874,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4239,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":216114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 3 because 1 + 2 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1162,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":217278,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":10635,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":227913,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 4 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 6 = 4.","rt":414,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":228328,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If  the sum  is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"12","response_history":["12"],"rt":4898,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":233227,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0 because 4 + 2 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":428,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":233656,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3547,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":237204,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 2 because 0 + 2 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":868,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":238073,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4482,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":242556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2 because 3 + 5 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":560,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":243118,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br / ><br />  (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":246661,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 because 1 + 4 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":445,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":247107,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3427,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":250535,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0 because 5 + 1 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":412,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":250948,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3082,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":254031,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 1 because 1 + 0 = 1 and 1 is less than 6.","rt":854,"trial_type":"fee dback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":254886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2710,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":257597,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 1 because 5 + 2 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":515,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":258113,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a spec ial way  under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":5272,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":263386,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":1003,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":264390,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 u nder +<s ub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":17115,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":281506,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":645,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":282152,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1855,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":284008,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":530,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":284539,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":1904,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":286443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":438,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":286883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"8","response_history":["8"],"rt":6935,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":293818,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2599,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":296418,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2697,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":299117,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":550,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":299667,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":2989,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":302657,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<su b>6</sub > 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":928,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":303586,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4070,"trial_type":"que stion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":307657,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":2667,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":310326,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2291,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":312618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</su b> 5 +<s ub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1216,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":313834,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2051,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":315886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":863,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":316750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":1667,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":318417,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":671,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":319089,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br / ><br />D o you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":1408,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":320498,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"10","response_history":["10"],"rt":8731,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":329230,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":2298,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":331529,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3719,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":335249,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2\n","2"],"rt":9046,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":344296,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4362,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":348659,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":1849,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":350510,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3766,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":354277,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. 4 + 1 is 5 which is smaller than 9 so that 5 is the answer.","response_history":["5. 4 + 5","5. 4 + 1 is 5 which is smaller than 9 so that 5 is the answer."],"rt":19143,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":373421,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. 8+4 is 12 which is larger than nine so you subtract 9 and have 3 left","response_history":["3. 8+4 is 12 which is larger than nine so you subr","3. 8+4 is 12 which is larger than nine so you subtract 9 and have 3 left"],"rt":23476,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":396898,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":6105,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":403004,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":9234,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":412239,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"10","response_history":["10"],"rt":5090,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":417330,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2693,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":420024,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"12. 12 is the total of 9+3","response_history":["10. ","10.","10","1","12. 12 is the total of 6 _ 6","12. 12 is the total of 6 _ ","12. 12 is the to tal of 6  _","12. 12 is the total of 6 _","12. 12 is the total of 6 ","12. 12 is the total of 6","12. 12 is the total of 9_","12. 12 is the total of 9+3"],"rt":33416,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":453441,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no. I am not sure","response_history":["no. I am not sure"],"rt":6290,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":459732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I really don't know","response_history":["I really don't know"],"rt":4470,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":464203,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I do not think so","response_history":["I do not think so"],"rt":3825,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":468029,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I do not think so, I am not sure","response_history":["I do not think so, I amn","I do not think so, I am not sure"],"rt":6477,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":474506,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other cou nting nu mber you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":6193,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":480700,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+2","response_history":["1=","1+2"],"rt":26664,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":507365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I do not understand","response_history":["I do not understand"],"rt":7299,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":514665,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I am not sure","response_history":["I am not sure"],"rt":3789,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":518455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":3476,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":521932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","Fal se"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":2723,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":89,"time_elapsed":524656,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":1603,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":90,"time_elapsed":526261,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I do not know, I am confused","response_history":["I do not know, I am confused"],"rt":6100,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":91,"time_elapsed":532361,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":2826,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":92,"time_elapsed":535188,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I do not even understand any of this","response_history":["I do not even undeer","I do not even undee","I do not even understand any of this"],"rt":7786,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":93,"time_elapsed":542975,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":4319,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":94,"time_elapsed":547296,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1343,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":95,"time_elapsed":548640,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"24","response_history":["24"],"rt":1635,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":96,"time_elapsed":550276,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":3331,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":97,"time_elapsed":553608,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Statistics in College","response_history":["Statistics in College"],"rt":9043,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":98,"time_elapsed":562652,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How fa miliar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4339,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":99,"time_elapsed":566992,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","response_history":["1 - never heard of it","3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":4483,"trial_type":" question ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":100,"time_elapsed":571476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2706,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":101,"time_elapsed":574184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2131,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":102,"time_elapsed":576316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2347,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":103,"time_elapsed":578664,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":104,"time_elapsed":580376,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":2684,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":105,"time_elapsed":583061,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2670,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":106,"time_elapsed":585732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"This was very confusing to me","response_history":["This was very confusing to me"],"rt":5175,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":107,"time_elapsed":590908,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]